<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><csw:GetDomainResponse xmlns:csw="http://www.opengis.net/cat/csw/2.0.2" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dct="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:ows="http://www.opengis.net/ows/1.1" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.opengis.net/cat/csw/2.0.2 http://localhost:8080/geoserver/schemas/csw/2.0.2/CSW-discovery.xsd"><csw:DomainValues type="csw:Record"><csw:PropertyName>Abstract</csw:PropertyName><csw:ListOfValues><csw:Value>A simple rectangular polygon covering most of the world, it's only used for the purpose of providing a background (WMS bgcolor could be used instead)</csw:Value><csw:Value>Cities in Tasmania (actually, just the capital)</csw:Value><csw:Value>Digital elevation model for the Spearfish region.&#13;
&#13;
sfdem is a Tagged Image File Format with Geographic information</csw:Value><csw:Value>Highly simplified road layout of Manhattan in New York..</csw:Value><csw:Value>Italian sample mosaic</csw:Value><csw:Value>Main Tasmania roads</csw:Value><csw:Value>Manhattan landmarks, identifies water, lakes, parks, interesting buildilngs</csw:Value><csw:Value>Pk50095 is a raster file accompanied by a spatial data file.</csw:Value><csw:Value>Points of interest in New York, New York (on Manhattan). One of the attributes contains the name of a file with a picture of the point of interest.</csw:Value><csw:Value>Sample data from GRASS, archeological sites location, Spearfish, South Dakota, USA</csw:Value><csw:Value>Sample data from GRASS, bug sites location, Spearfish, South Dakota, USA</csw:Value><csw:Value>Sample data from GRASS, restricted areas, Spearfish, South Dakota, USA</csw:Value><csw:Value>Sample data from GRASS, road layout, Spearfish, South Dakota, USA</csw:Value><csw:Value>Sample data from GRASS, streams, Spearfish, South Dakota, USA</csw:Value><csw:Value>Spearfish City in Lawrence County, South Dakota&#13;
&#13;
The area covered by the data set is in the vicinity of Spearfish and includes a majority of the Black Hills National Forest (i.e., Mount Rushmore).</csw:Value><csw:Value>Tasmania Australia from Digital Chart of the World.</csw:Value><csw:Value>Tasmania state boundaries</csw:Value><csw:Value>Tasmania water bodies</csw:Value><csw:Value>This is some census data on the states.</csw:Value><csw:Value>Topologically Integrated Geographic Encoding and Referencing (TIGER) dataset for New York.</csw:Value></csw:ListOfValues></csw:DomainValues></csw:GetDomainResponse>